Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, circa 1890-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Over 1,353 images
    - CSA -- Building; Library, 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, negative (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folder 21)
      P1983.0035
    - CSA -- Building; School Library, 1973-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 22-23)
      P1981.0668A-B
    - CSA -- Building; School Library, 1973-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 2 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 24-25)
      P1981.1042A-B
    - CSA -- Building; Student Caf, circa 1970's; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folder 26)
      P1983.0137
    - CSA -- Building; Construction of Sculpture Studio in old Boiler Room, 1978-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 4 prints; 3 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 27-30)
      P1981.0667A-D
    - CSA -- Building; Opening of the New Student Lounge, July 1963; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 negatives (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 31-35)
      P1981.0377A-E
    - CSA -- Children's Programs; Saturday School, 1966-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 10 negatives (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 36-45)
      P1981.0375A-J
    - CSA -- Children's Programs; Saturday School, 1966-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print, contact sheet; 3 prints; 5 prints; 4 prints; 3 prints, contact sheet; 5 prints; 4 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 46-52)
      P1981.0684A-G
    - CSA -- Maine Workshops; Maine Workshops, 1979-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folders 53-54)
      P1981.0666A-B
    - CSA -- Maine Workshops; Maine Workshops, 1979-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 10 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folder 55)
      P1981.0665
    - CSA -- Maine Workshops; Maine Workshops, 1979-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 9, Flat box 43, Folder 56)
      P1981.1234
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 1st Annual Champagne Brunch given by the Class of 1981, April 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 1-2)
      P1981.0750A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Ballon Event staged by the students near the Washington Monument, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 3)
      P1981.0737
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Baltimore Masters, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 2 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 4-5)
      P1981.1048A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Disabled Persons Poster Contest, 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 6 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 6)
      P1981.0741
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Federal Home Loan Board Building Construction Site, circa 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 7)
      P1981.1060
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Foundation Class--Black Tie Luncheon, December 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 7 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 8)
      P1983.0099
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Lady Sarah Project, September 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 3 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 9-11)
      P1981.0744A-C
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Masquerade in the Park (foundation students), April 1973; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, 2 prints; 8 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 12-13)
      P1981.1046A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Open House of the School, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 14)
      P1981.0736
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Open Studio Day, April 1974; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets; 5 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 15-16)
      P1981.1047A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; School Fundraiser, 1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 17)
      P1981.0742
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Students help Gene Davis paint the Magic Circle in the Rotunda for the 34th, 26 February 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 18)
      P1981.0745
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Swiss Embassy Fund Raiser, May 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 19)
      P1981.0746
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; The Gala Auction, 5 November 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 contact sheets; 10 prints; 12 prints; 9 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 20-23)
      P1981.0103A-D
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; The Gala Auction, 5 November 1977; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 3 prints (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 24-25)
      P1981.0743A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Visual Communications Conference, 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folder 26)
      P1981.1045
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Women's Committee presents Litho press gift to the School, 1975; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 3 negative strips (Box 9, Flat box 44, Folders 27-28)
      P1981.1066A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 1st Beaux Art Ball Committee Meeting, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 1)
      P1981.0740
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 2 Unknown Visiting Artists Critiqueing Students' Work, 1978-1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 10, Folder 2)
      P1981.0831
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 2nd Annual Champagne Brunch (Class of 1981), 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 3)
      P1981.0747
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Affordable Art Auction, 9 June 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 negatives, contact sheet, print (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 4)
      P1983.0015
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Affordable art Sale, 23 June 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, 2 prints; negative (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 5-6)
      P1981.1072A-B
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Barry Johnston's Sculpture Competition, June 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print, 3 contact sheets (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 7)
      P1981.0714
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Beaux Arts Marquerade Ball, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 8)
      P1981.0738
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Beaux Arts Marquerade Ball, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 9-9.1)
      P1981.0040
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Beaux Arts Masquerade Ball, 12 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; (A empty); 2 contact sheet; 2 negatives; 13 prints; 2 contact sheets; 2 contact sheets (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 10-15)
      P1981.0683A-F
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Beaux Arts Masquerade Ball, 12 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints, 6 contact sheets; 2 contact sheets, 8 prints; 4 cs; 4 negatives, 4 prints; cs; 4 cs; 3 cs (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 16-22)
      P1981.0009A-H
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Bizzarre Bazzar, 8 December 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; negative, contact sheet (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 23)
      P1983.0103
    - CSA -- Benifita, Special Events; Graduation--Class of 1979, May 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 24)
      P1981.0739
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Opening of Ethel's Saloon, 1979-1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 25)
      P1981.0748
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Pizza Bakeoff, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 26)
      P1981.0749
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Portfolio Day, 12 December 1982; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 contact sheets, 4 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 27)
      P1983.0104
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Portfolio Day--A Career Day in the Arts, 14 December 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 17 color prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 28)
      P1981.0735
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Thank You Party for Philip Merril, September 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 29)
      P1983.0107
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; The Corcoran School Decorates the White House Christmas Tree, 9 December 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; 35 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 30-38)
      P1981.0682A-I
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Video Arcade, 18 February 1983; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 3 prints; 5 contact sheets (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folders 39-41)
      P1983.0219A-C
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 1998 Awards Ceremony, Series 1 subseries 1; 21 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 7)
      P1999.0027
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 1998 Awards Ceremony, Series 1 subseries 1; 4 contact sheets (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 2)
      P1999.0026
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; 1998 Awards Ceremony, Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 3)
      P1999.0025
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Commencement, 1996; Series 1 subseries 1; 50 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 4)
      P1999.0030
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Commencement, 1996; Series 1 subseries 1; 44 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 5)
      P1999.0028
    - CSA -- Benefits, Special Events; Commencement, 1996; Series 1 subseries 1; 27 prints (Box 10, Flat box 45.5, Folder 6)
      P1999.0029
    - CSA -- Exhibits; 1964 Concours, Subseries 1.1; 6 prints (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 1)
      1983.0236
    - CSA -- Exhibits; 1st Semester Student Show, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 negatives (Box 10, Flat box 45, Folder 2)
      P1981.1058
    - CSA -- Exhibits; 4th Year Student Exhibit, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 3)
      P1981.0688
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Dupont Center Student Show, April 1973; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 11 negative strips (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folders 4-5)
      P1981.1056A-B
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Student Art Show Outdoor/Office Exhibition, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 4 negative strips (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folders 6-7)
      P1981.1059
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Student Exhibits at Dupont Center, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; negative (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folders 8-9)
      P1981.1057A-B
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Student Gallery at Dupont Center, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 10)
      P1983.0134
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Student Gallery at Dupont Center, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 11)
      P1983.0135
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Students installing show, 1971-1972; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 12)
      P1981.0361
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Students Installing Student Photo Exhibit, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folder 13)
      P1981.0689
    - CSA -- Exhibits; Students installing their exhibit, April 1971; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints; 4 prints; 3 prints (Box 10, Flat box 46, Folders 14-16)
      P1981.0360A-C
    - CSA -- Art Work; Artwork by Corcoran Students, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; 29 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folders 1-7)
      P1981.0109
    - CSA -- Art Work; Drawing, Fine Art III, 1975-1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 8)
      P1983.0133
    - CSA -- Art Work; Drawing, Fine Art III, 1975-1976; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 9)
      P1983.0132
    - CSA -- Art Work; Drawing, Fine Art III, 1975-1976; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 10)
      P1983.0131
    - CSA -- Art Work; James E. Williams Walton's Class, circa 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 11)
      P1983.0274
    - CSA -- Art Work; One Student's Work brought into Dupont Center, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 22)
      P1981.1052
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student Art Work Chair Project, Dupont Center, 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; 4 negative strips (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folders 23-24)
      P1981.1054A-B
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student Artwork, January 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; negative (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 25)
      P1981.1051
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student artwork--costumes, 1973; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 26)
      P1981.0685
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student with her artwork at the Dupont Center Building, 1975-1976; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 27)
      P1981.0368
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student Work (Unidentified), 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet; negative (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folders 28-29)
      P1981.1053A-B
    - CSA -- Art Work; Student Work (Unidentified), 1973-1974; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet, 5 negative strips (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folders 30-31)
      P1981.1055A-B
    - CSA -- Art Work; Unidentified student Artwork, 1977-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; 5 prints; 4 prints; 6 prints; 4 prints; 4 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folders 32-36)
      P1981.0833A-E
    - CSA -- Art Work; Unidentified Student Painting Class, circa 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 37)
      P1983.0245
    - CSA -- Art Work; Unidentified Student Painting Class, circa 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 38)
      P1983.0246
    - CSA -- Art Work; Unidentified Student Painting Class, circa 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 39)
      P1983.0244
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Debra Tatman, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 40)
      P1981.0607
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Diane Zak, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 41)
      P1981.0653
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Gretchen Williams, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 42)
      P1981.0651
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Jackie Shaffer, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 43)
      P1981.0530
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by James L. Thomas, 1950-1952; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 44)
      P1983.0226
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by James Suzuki, 1954-1955; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 45)
      P1983.0233
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by James Suzuki, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 46)
      P1983.0273
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Jin O. Yang, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 47)
      P1981.0652
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Joan Wilkinson, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print; negative (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 48-49)
      P1981.0582A-B
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Linda Zylich, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 50)
      P1981.0515
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Ling Wong, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 51)
      P1981.0610
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Magurite Welch, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 52)
      P1981.0609
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Peter Viscardi, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 53)
      P1981.0608
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Richard Skinner, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 54)
      P1981.0606
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Rita Wen-Ying Sun, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 55)
      P1981.0531
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Sarah Schneiderman, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 56)
      P1981.0605
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Sarah Tuft, 1978; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 57)
      P1981.0687
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Scott Von Bergener, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 58)
      P1981.0585
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Theo Shafer, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 59)
      P1981.0649
    - CSA -- Art Work; Works by Pamela Turner, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 10, Flat box 47, Folder 60)
      P1981.0650
    - Art Rental; "Art and Offices", 1967; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 1)
      P1983.0116
    - Art Rental; Art Rental Gallery, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 2)
      P1983.0115
    - Art Rental; Art Rental Gallery Model, October 1967; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 negatives; negative (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folders 3-4)
      P1981.1034A-B
    - Art Rental; Designer Rooms, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 11, Flat box 47, Folder 5)
      P1983.0114
    - Art Rental; Display, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; contact sheet (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 6)
      P1983.0119
    - Art Rental; Display, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 7)
      P1983.0120
    - Art Rental; Display, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 8)
      P1983.0121
    - Art Rental; Display by Dorthy Griffith Assoc., circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; 4 prints (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 9)
      P1983.0117
    - Art Rental; Display by John J. Greer Assoc., circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 10)
      P1983.0122
    - Art Rental; Display by John Peter Incourd, circa 1960's; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints; 2 contact sheets (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folders 11-12)
      P1983.0118A-B
    - Art Rental; Lord and Taylor Exhibit at Art Rental Gallery Service, 1962; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 negatives (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 13)
      P1981.1035
    - Art Rental; Ray Bates shows Mrs. Wiley Buchanan and Dir. Williams his Art, 26 June 1962; Series 1 subseries 1; 2 prints (Box 11, Flat box 48, Folder 14)
      P1983.0123
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Brad Anderson, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 1)
      P1981.0583
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Dorothy Andrake, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 2)
      P1981.0532
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by James T. Arth, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 3)
      P1981.0516
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Jack Arthur, 1956-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 4)
      P1983.0232
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Joel Arwine, 1962-1964; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 5)
      P1983.0229
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by John Atkins, 1960-1965; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 6)
      P1983.0231
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Mildred Baldwin, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 7)
      P1981.0584
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Rhonda Bates, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 8)
      P1981.0517
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Ethel Bernstein, 1950-1960; Series 1 subseries 1; 3 prints (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 9)
      P1981.0612
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Connie Bigelow, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 10)
      P1981.0586
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Sylvia Boncesco, 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 11)
      P1983.0239
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Sylvia Bowyer, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 12)
      P1981.0587
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Dianne Briggs, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 13)
      P1981.0523
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Elizabeth Buelte, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 14)
      P1981.0518
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Kendall Buster, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 15)
      P1981.0519
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Peggy Carter, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 16)
      P1981.0636
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Bruce N. Cheeks, 1962; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 17)
      P1983.0225
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Jean Chenette, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 18)
      P1981.0520
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by John Clendenning, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 19)
      P1983.0271
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Ehian Yoon Cho, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 20)
      P1981.0588
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Celia Conlon, undated; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 21)
      P1983.0228
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by C. Albert Constanzo, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 22)
      P1981.0589
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by A. G. Corbett, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 23)
      P1981.0637
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Thelma Costikyan, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 24)
      P1983.0270
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Frank Cunningham, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 25)
      P1981.0590
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Pat Dalzell, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 26)
      P1981.0591
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Karen Davis, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 27)
      P1981.0638
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by David O. Decker, 1964; Series 1 subseries 1; 8 prints (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 28)
      P1983.0174
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Neil Doherty, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 29)
      P1981.0639
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Ann Doran, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; drawing (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 30)
      P1981.0640
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Arianne Dubois, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 31)
      P1981.0592
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Janet Dunphy, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 32)
      P1981.0593
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Don Fear, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 33)
      P1981.0533
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Wayne Fitzpatrick, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 34)
      P1981.0594
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Phil Frisbee, 1979; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 35)
      P1981.0641
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Gay Gladding, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 36)
      P1983.0224
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Eugene Green, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 37)
      P1981.0513
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Bill Harvey, 1979-1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 38)
      P1981.0791
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Elizabeth Hecht, 1955-1956; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 39)
      P1983.0237
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Patricia Helsing, 1980; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 40)
      P1981.0595
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Daria Hill, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 41)
      P1983.0269
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Timothea Howard, 1979; Subseries 1.1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 42)
      P1981.0642
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Ramiro Jarrin, 1981; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 43)
      P1981.0534
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Rita Jaskowitz, 1980; Series 1 subseries 11; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 44)
      P1981.0596
    - CSA -- Art Work; Work by Richard B. Keen, 1960-1961; Series 1 subseries 1; print (Box 11, Flat box 49, Folder 45)
      P1983.0272